BAYU WIJAYA

Mobile Application Developer

+6285871500098



bayu_wpp@outlook.com



bayuwijdev.github.io



SUMMARY

Mobile Application Developer with 7+ years of experience. Have a passion for software development and skills in Android Development, iOS Development, and Flutter Development. And also good at building a class library or SDK for native and framework flutter.

EDUCATION

Indonesia Computer University

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering 2013 – 2017

BILOGIX Certification

Building App for Android 2017

SMK Merdeka Bandung

Computer and Network Engineering 2010 – 2013

SKILLS

- Flutter Development
- Android Development
- · iOS Development
- Git
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- · Experience in Scrum Methodology

ACHIEVEMENT

- Finalist in the International APICTA 2016 Competition
- 2nd Winner of National Gemastik 9 2016
- Finalist of BRI Digital Challange 2016

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mobile Application Developer

MNC Innovation Center | 2020 - Present

- Joined with RnD team to research, develop and maintenance research products MNC Group.
- Review, develop, maintenance and documentation library and application projects of business unit of MNC Group.
- Supports unit business products for enhancement and research needs

Projects : InnoPlayer, MNC Identifier, SES Audio Editor, Cubicle Video Editor, Vision+ Android TV

Mobile Application Developer

Paytren | 2018 - 2020

- Responsible for development and maintenance android and iOS apps.
- Develop, maintenance and documentation library and application projects.
- Research in android & iOS architecture and technology and then sharing to the team.

Projects : Paytren 5.17 Android, Paytren 5.17 iOS, Paytren Connect (TConn) iOS

Android Developer

Paytren | 2017 - 2018

- Develop and maintenance various apps, and also security library android
- Maintenance including fixing bugs and some enhance in applications.
- Research in android technology.

Projects: Paytren 5.17 Android, Paytren EDC Android